Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Undated Material from Various Campaigns, 1800s-2000s
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1928 or 1932
    - Pin shaped like elephant with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-003)
    - Pin red white and blue, word: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-004)
    - Pin rectangle blue and gold, word: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-005)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Hoover and Curtis, 1928 or 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-006)
    - Metal pin, word: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-007)
    - Metal elephant pin, word: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-008)
    - Red elephant pin, words: Hoover and Curtis, 1928 or 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-009)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Hoover and text: Herbert Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-010)
    - Pin with red, white and blue stripes with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-011)
    - Pin with red, white and blue stripes with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-012)
    - Pin with blue rim with printed photograph of Hoover and text: A Democrat for Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-013)
    - Pin gold with eagle and text: Hoover Curtis, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-014)
    - Pin white, with text: Hoover and Curtis, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-015)
    - Pin with elephant on top of a ball with text: Hoover GOP, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-016)
    - Pin with red, white and blue stripes with text: Hoover Glenn Small, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-017)
    - Oval pin with red, white and blue stripes with text: Hoover Loyal Republican, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-018)
    - Pin white, with text: Hoover and Curtis, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-019)
    - Oval pin with gold and red, with text: Hoover for President, Our Favorite, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-020)
    - Rectangle pin in blue with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-021)
    - Rectangle pin in blue with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-022)
    - Rectangle pin in blue with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-023)
    - Rectangle pin with red, white and blue stripes, with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-024)
    - Rectangle pin with red, white and blue stripes, with text: Hoover, 1928 or 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH19xx-025)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1930s or 1940s
    - Tin coin with Roosevelt's portrait on the recto; text on the verso: Our Twenty Second President, Inaugurated 1933 … Charm Candy, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-001)
    - Button with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: A Gallant Leader Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-002)
    - Button with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: A Gallant Leader Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-003)
    - Button with printed photograph of Roosevelt and ribbon/donkey attached, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-004)
    - Pin portrait for Roosevelt, words: I Am For Roosevelt, Labor's Non-Partisan League of Conn., 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-005)
    - Pin portrait of Roosevelt, words: I want Roosevelt Again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-006)
    - Pin white, words: A Pauper for Roosevelt, in blue, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-007)
    - Pin white, with dice, words: You lose Franklin, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-008)
    - Pin white, words: Strike three F. D. you're out, in red, 1940 or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-009)
    - Pin blue, word: Roosevelt, in white, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-010)
    - Pin red with white stripe with FDR in blue, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-011)
    - Pin blue, word: Roosevelt, in white, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-012)
    - Pin blue, word: Roosevelt, in white, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-013)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Roosevelt for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-014)
    - Pin blue rim, with printed photograph of Roosevelt with text: Re-elect Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-015)
    - Pin with American flag and word: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-016)
    - Pin white, with American flag in shield, with word: Roosevelt, in blue, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-017)
    - Pin red, white, and blue stripes, with text: We Want Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-018)
    - Pin (small), with red, white, and blue stripes, with text: F.D.R., 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-019)
    - Pin red and white stripes, with text: We want FDR Again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-020)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt and donkey attached, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-021)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-022)
    - Pin navy blue, with text: Youth for Roosevelt, in white, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-023)
    - Pin (large) with printed photograph of Roosevelt, ribbon and donkey attached, and words: Re-elect Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-024)
    - Pin (small) with blue and white stripes and text: FDR, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-025)
    - Pin (small) red, white, and blue stripes, with text: I Want Roosevelt Again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-026)
    - Navy Blue Button (small) with horseshoe and text: Four More Lucky Years; Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-027)
    - Navy Blue Button with portrait of Roosevelt, and text: Re-Elect Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-028)
    - Pin with blue border and printed photograph of Roosevelt in shield with flag border, ribbon and donkey attached, with words: Re-elect Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-029)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: A Gallant Leader, Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-030)
    - Pin with American flag and word: Roosevelt, in blue, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-031)
    - Pin with blue border and white stars, with word: Roosevelt, in red, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-032)
    - Pin navy blue, with word: Roosevelt, in white, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-033)
    - Pin red, with printed photograph of Roosevelt and word: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-034)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt for Ex-President, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-035)
    - Pin white, with text: I want to be a captain too, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-036)
    - Pin green, with text: We want Roosevelt to abdicate, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-037)
    - Pin white, with text: One party nation? Nothing doing, Franklin!, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-038)
    - Pin black, with text: We don't want Eleanor either!, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-039)
    - Pin white, with text: Sure I'll vote for Roosevelt Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-040)
    - Pin white, with text: One party nation? Nothing doing, Franklin!, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-041)
    - Pin white, with text: Eleanor? No soap!, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-042)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt for Ex-President, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-043)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt for Ex-President, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-044)
    - Pin, printed photograph of Roosevelt, with ribbon attached, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-045)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-046)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt for Ex-President, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-047)
    - Pin white, with text: No Franklin the first, 1940 or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-048)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt is buying the Aquacade to keep Eleanor Holme, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-049)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt for Ex-President, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-050)
    - Pin white, with text: Roosevelt for Ex-President, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-051)
    - Pin green, with text: Napoleon met his Waterloo Frank, you will too, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-052)
    - Pin blue, with text: Roosevelt for president, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-053)
    - Pin red, white, and blue stripes, with text: We want Roosevelt, with ribbon and donkey head pin attached, with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-054)
    - Pin pink, with text: Eleanor? No soap!, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-055)
    - Pin white (large), with text: Papa - "I wanna be a captain too", 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-056)
    - Pin white (large), with text: We don't want Eleanor either, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 28, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-057)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Roosevelt with word: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-058)
    - Pin red, white, and blue stripes, with text: We want Roosevelt Again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-059)
    - Pin white, with green text: No crown for Franklin, 1940 or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-060)
    - Pin blue, with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-061)
    - Pin blue, with text: Teamsters Support Roosevelt Program, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-062)
    - Pin blue rim, with text: Carry on FDR, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-063)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of FDR and text: Re-elect our President, Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-064)
    - Pin white, with American flag in shield, with word: Roosevelt, in blue, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-065)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Roosevelt, with text: Roosevelt for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-066)
    - Pin with American flag, with printed photographs of Roosevelt and Garner, with text: Roosevelt, Garner, 1932 or 1936 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-067)
    - Pin with American flag border, with printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-068)
    - Pin with American flag emblems, with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-069)
    - Pin with red stripes, with text: We Want FDR, ACWA, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-070)
    - Pin white (large), with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Franklin D. Roosevelt for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-071)
    - Pin with printed colorized photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-072)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Roosevelt, and text: Our Leader Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-073)
    - Pin red, with printed photograph of Roosevelt and word: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-074)
    - Pin with blue border and text: Re-elect Roosevelt, his heart is with the people, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-075)
    - Litho tab white, with text: Roosevelt now more than ever, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-076)
    - Pin white with blue border, printed photograph of Roosevelt, black ribbon, and text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-077)
    - Pin gold, with raised profiles of Roosevelt and Garner, and text: Franklin D. Roosevelt, John N. Garner, 1932 or 1936 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-078)
    - Pin with American flag emblems, with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-079)
    - Silver donkey with attached white ribbon, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-080)
    - Pin silver with raised profile of Roosevelt and text: President of the United States, Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-081)
    - Pin gold, with raised profiles of Roosevelt and Garner, and text: A New Day, A New Deal, Franklin D. Roosevelt, John N. Garner, 1932 or 1936 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-082)
    - Pin red, with red image of rooster and text: Just Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-083)
    - Pin gold, with raised profiles of Roosevelt and Garner, and text: A New Day, A New Deal, Franklin D. Roosevelt, John N. Garner, 1932 or 1936 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-084)
    - Pin with American flag emblems, with gold border with eagle and attached ribbon, and text: Roosevelt, Garner, 1932 or 1936 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-085)
    - Pin white, with text: A Pauper for Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-086)
    - Pin with red and blue border, with text: Team with Roosevelt, I. B. of T. C.S. & H. of A., 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-087)
    - Pin with red, white and blue stripes, and text: I want Roosevelt again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-088)
    - Plastic white donkey, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-089)
    - Litho tab metal, with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-090)
    - Litho tab blue, with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-091)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-092)
    - Pin with red stripes, with text: I Want FDR Again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-093)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-094)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-095)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-096)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, with ribbon and donkey pin attached with text: Dem, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-097)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Happy Birthday, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-098)
    - Pin with red border and printed photograph of Roosevelt with text: Re-elect Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-099)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-100)
    - Pin with blue quadrants and red text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-101)
    - Pin blue with text: Labor wants Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-102)
    - Pin with blue border and printed photograph of Roosevelt with text: Labor's Non-partisan League, Roosevelt for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-103)
    - Pin with red border and printed photograph of Roosevelt with text: Roosevelt, He's good enough for my buck, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-104)
    - Pin with blue border and printed photograph of Roosevelt with text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-105)
    - Pin white with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Roosevelt for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-106)
    - Pin with red, white and blue stripes, and text: I want Roosevelt again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-107)
    - Pin blue with horseshoe and text: Roosevelt, four more lucky years, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-108)
    - Pin with blue border and text: Re-elect Roosevelt, his heart is with the people, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-109)
    - Pin white with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Franklin D. Roosevelt, A Gallant Leader, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 29, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-110)
    - Pin silver with blue stripe and text: Vote for Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-111)
    - Pin with red, white and blue stripes, and text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-112)
    - Pin with red border with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: American Labor Party, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-113)
    - Pin red (small) with text: Re-elect President Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-114)
    - Pin with American flag emblems and text: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-115)
    - Pin white with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Franklin D. Roosevelt for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-116)
    - Pin with red and blue border, with text: Roosevelt Deputy, The Union of Democratic Clubs, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-117)
    - Pin white (small) with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: OK PAC, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-118)
    - Pin with red, white, and blue stripes, with text: Roosevelt Davey, 1932 or 1936 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-119)
    - Pin with red and blue border, with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Carry on with Roosevelt, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-120)
    - Pin with red border and printed photograph of Roosevelt, with text: Roosevelt more than ever, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-121)
    - Paper pin white (large) with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Vote Straight Democratic, Keep Pennsylvania Liberal, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-122)
    - Pin bronze (small), with text: Roosevelt Garner, 1932 or 1936 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-123)
    - Pin white and blue, with text: Vote for Clark Roosevelt Park and Entire Democratic Ticket, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-124)
    - Pin white and blue, with text: Support Dr. C. J. Satti for Secy. of State, Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-125)
    - Pin white and blue, with text: Support C. C. Swartz for Comptroller, Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-126)
    - Pin silver, with profile of Roosevelt with text: Franklin Delano Roosevelt, For Defense for President, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-127)
    - Pin (small), with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: F.D.R., 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-128)
    - Pin green, with gold star and text: Roosevelt Garner Club, Minnesota, 1932 or 1936 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-129)
    - Pin green, with gold star and text: Roosevelt Garner Club, Ohio, 1932 or 1936 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-130)
    - Pin green, with gold star and text: Roosevelt Garner Club, Pennsylvania, 1932 or 1936 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-131)
    - Paper insert (small), with blue border, printed photograph of Roosevelt and Arabic script, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-132)
    - Cardboard tab with text: FDR, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-133)
    - Cardboard tab with text: FDR, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-134)
    - Pin with red stripes, with text: We want FDR again, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-135)
    - Pin red, with image of rooster and text: Just Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-136)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Roosevelt in square frame over red, white, and blue V, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR19xx-137)
    - Bumper sticker: Roosevelt, 1932, 1936, 1940, or 1944 (Box 13)
  - Dewey, Thomas Edmund, 1940s
    - Pin portrait of Dewey, words: Go Forth (4th) With Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-001)
    - Pin white, word: Dewey, in blue, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-002)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Dewey For President, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-003)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Dewey For President, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-004)
    - Pin white, words: Dewey The Racket Buster New Deal Buster, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-005)
    - Pin portrait of Dewey, black and white, words: For President Thomas E. Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-006)
    - Pin portrait of Dewey, black and white, words: Thomas E. Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-007)
    - Pin with blue eagle over word: Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-008)
    - Pin portrait of Dewey, blue, red outside with words: For President Thomas E. Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-009)
    - Pin portrait of Dewey, two elephants, words: For President Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-010)
    - Pin white, words: Phooey on Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-011)
    - Pin white with broom, words: Clean House with Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-012)
    - Large pin portrait of Dewey, black and white, words: For President Thomas E. Dewey, 1944 or 1948 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED19xx-013)
  - Russell, Richard Brevard, 1940s
    - Button with text: Elect Russell President, 1948 or 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-RBR19xx-001)
    - Button with text: Elect Russell President, 1948 or 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-RBR19xx-002)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David, 1950s
    - Button with text: I Like Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-001)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-002)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-003)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-004)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-005)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-006)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-007)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-008)